

Bilge Bahar Saatçi

ARCHITECTURE STUDENT

Details

Istayson St. Ozsistem Manolya Houses no 25, İstanbul/Tuzla region, Turkey +905366401427 bilgebahar2000@hotmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

AutoCAD

Autodesk 3ds Max

Autodesk Revit

Adobe Photoshop

Rihno

SketchUp

Hobbies

Painting, Baglama playing

Languages

English

Japanese

Turkish

Profile

As an architecture student, I have a strong passion for designing and creating functional and aesthetically pleasing buildings and other structures. I have experience with a variety of design software, including AutoCAD and SketchUp, and I have completed projects that showcase my creative abilities. In addition, I have knowledge of building codes and regulations, and I am familiar with sustainable design principles and techniques. I am committed to continuing my education and professional development in the field of architecture. You can find my portfolio here: https://bahar-saatci.github.io/portfolio/

Experience

Architecture Internhsip at Studio Tecnico Pugliese, Terranova Da Sibari

JUNE 2022 — SEPTEMBER 2022

The internship took place in Italy and I worked with the Italian Architecture Office. I have learned to use design software, gained a deeper understanding of Italian architecture, and developed my communication and collaboration skills. I have also worked on a variety of design projects, gaining a deep appreciation for the art and science of architecture.

Architecture Internship at Dinamik Insaat Arhitecture, Tekirdağ

SEPTEMBER 2021 — OCTOBER 2022

During the internship i worked along with Dilek Kizday who has 30 years of architectural experience. I have gained hands-on experience in the field of design and construction and it was overall a great experience. By the end of the internship I managed to design a villa and build it using AutoCAD and Revit.

Architecture Internship at Sadunoğlu Architecture Office, Tekirdağ

JUNE 2021 — SEPTEMBER 2021

This was my first internship in the field of architecture and it provided me great insights of what an architect does. It was a valuable opportunity for me to gain a wide range of skills and experiences.

Education

Slovak University of Technology - Winter Term as an erasmus exchange student, Bratislava

SEPTEMBER 2022 — FEBRUARY 2023

Bachelor, Gebze Technical University, Istanbul

2018 — PRESENT

Yengec art KADIKOY (Paint Education by Artist Ilsu Aslan)

2018 - 2020

Kartal Sinav Temel Highschool

2017 — 2018

Çanakkale Fen (Science) Highschool

2014 - 2017

Courses, Certifications and Awards

Ever After Workshop-PIA LAB-3th WINNER, Tokyo

AUGUST 1, 2020 — AUGUST 9, 2020

PIA LAB, Ishinomaki Laboratory, Tokyo University Of Arts and Politecnico Di Milano organised the international 'Ever After Workshop' through online platforms. As team 5, we won the contest. I had the chance to compete with architecture students from different parts of the world. At the end of the collective design process, our project was built and exhibited in Tokyo Design art. This competition gave me different architectural perspectives.

Japanese Education from Akio Kuwabara (N4-N3) -ILM

MARCH 2021 — JUNE 2021

Technic Drawing and 3D Expert Certification from CG Artist Yasin Safak

JANUARY 2020 — MAY 2020